11points.com 2019-04-17

# Privacy Policy and Disclosures

11 Points, a web site located at 11points.com, is owned and operated by Sam Greenspan, who values your privacy.

This privacy policy outlines the types of personal information that may be received or collected by this site, and how it is used. If you have any questions about this privacy policy, please feel free to send a message.

#### Information you voluntarily submit

Information you voluntarily submit 11points.com may collect information you submit, such as your name and e-mail address when you choose to send an e-mail message.

At no time should you submit any sensitive personal information to this website via any method. That includes information such as health information, financial information, or anything you deem personal and confidential. If you elect to submit such information, 11points.com cannot be responsible for it.

You can also request that 11points.com erase any personal data we hold about you. That does not include any data we are obliged to keep for administrative, legal, or security purposes.

#### Contacting 11 Points

There are several ways you may contact 11points.com, including by sending an e-mail or social media message. If you choose to contact the site, your message may, of course, include your information, such as your name, e-mail address, and/or phone number. Any personal contact information you choose to share will only be used to respond to you.

If you are sharing information for publication or for the purposes of 11points.com’s editorial content, that information may be published, and it may be attributed to you using your name.

Your personal information, such as your e-mail address or phone number, will not be publicly shared, unless you explicitly request that it be shared. And information submitted via the contact form or other methods will never be used for marketing purposes.

#### Contests

If you choose to enter a contest, contest information, such as a mailing address or e-mail address, will be used only as specified in the contest rules, such as to verify eligibility or to send you a prize, and may be provided to a third party or sponsor in order to send that prize. After the contest concludes, all personal information will be permanently deleted.

#### Newsletter

If you choose to subscribe to 11points.com’s e-mail newsletter, your e-mail address will be used to send you that newsletter. Newsletters are sent using Mailchimp, which stores your e-mail address in order to send you those messages. You can unsubscribe any time, using the link found in every message. Unsubscribing will permanently remove your e-mail address from 11points.com’s list of newsletter subscribers.

#### Children’s information

This site does not knowingly collect any personally identifiable information from children under the age of 18. If a parent or guardian becomes aware that their child has provided us with personally identifiable information without the consent of their parent or guardian, that parent or guardian should contact the site, and we will use our best efforts to promptly remove such information from any records.

#### Analytics and logs

11points.com uses Google Analytics to track usage of the website and information about visitors, such as pages that were visited or what web browsers people are using to visit the site. Any data that’s gathered will not be linked to any information that is personally identifiable, and your IP address will be anonymized by Google Analytics.

In order to ensure network and information security and prevent fraud, the web servers that host 11points.com may generate and store access, usage, and/or error logs, which may include IP addresses of visitors to the site. Only authorized personnel have access to those sever logs, and they are automatically deleted after seven days.

#### Cookies

Cookies may be set in your browser when you visit this website, including by third-party services and as described elsewhere in this Privacy Policy, in order to support advertising, social sharing, and other functions.

You can, at any time, prevent the setting of cookies by changing the settings in your web browser, including by permanently denying the setting of cookies. Furthermore, you may delete already set cookies at any time via your browser or other software programs.

#### Embedded content

Articles on this site may include embedded content, such as YouTube or Facebook videos or tweets from Twitter. Embedded content from other websites behaves in the exact same way as you’ve visited that website. Those websites may collect data about you, use cookies to provide their content, embed additional third-party tracking, and/or monitor your interaction with that embedded content, including tracing your interaction with the embedded content if you have an account and are logged in to that website.

#### Affiliate programs

This site may engage in affiliate marketing, which is done by embedding special tracking links. If you click on such a link for an affiliate partnership, a cookie may be placed in your browser to track any sales for purposes of commissions.

11points.com is a participant in the Amazon Services LLC Associates Program, an affiliate advertising program designed to provide a means for sites to earn advertising fees by advertising and links to Amazon.com. As part of the Amazon Associates program, the site may post customized links, provided by Amazon, to track referrals. This program utilizes cookies to track visits for the purposes of assigning commission on these sales.

No personally identifiable information will be received by 11points.com about any affiliate purchases.

#### Advertising

We may use third-party advertising networks and companies to serve advertisements when you visit the site, and those may use cookies. If you would like more information about this practice, or you would like to opt-in or opt-out of this data collection, please visit [optout.networkadvertising.org](http://optout.networkadvertising.org/).

As a result of your visit, ad server and traffic monitoring companies—including advertising networks and exchanges, traffic measurement service providers, marketing-analytics service providers, and others—may collect anonymous data. In addition, third-party advertising companies may use non-personally identifiable information about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide relevant ads.

Third-party advertising companies may use information about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology the advertisements and links that appear on 11points.com send directly to your browsers. Other technologies, such as cookies, JavaScript, or web beacons, may also be used by the third-party ad networks to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and/or to personalize the advertising content that you see.

Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on 11points.com. Google’s use of the DoubleClick cookie enables it and its partners to serve ads to users based on their visit to 11points.com and other sites on the Internet.

This site uses Google Opinion Rewards and complies under the Google polices as described [here](https://support.google.com/360suite/surveys/answer/2375134?hl=en) and Google’s [privacy policy](https://policies.google.com/privacy?hl=en). No information from those surveys is collected by nor shared with 11points.com.

You may: Control Google’s ad personalization by visiting [Google Ads Settings](https://www.google.com/settings/u/0/ads) … opt out via the Digital Advertising Alliance’s [WebChoices Tool](http://optout.aboutads.info/) … [limit Facebook ad tracking](https://www.facebook.com/help/568137493302217).

#### Third party use of information

11points.com itself has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers. 11points.com’s privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or web sites.

As noted elsewhere in this Privacy Policy, 11points.com uses third-party services to provide content and services to you. We may share your information with third parties when you explicitly authorize us to share your information.

Each third-party service provider’s use of information is dictated by their respective privacy policies. 11points.com currently uses the following third-party service providers: [TinyLetter/MailChimp](https://mailchimp.com/legal/privacy/), to send newsletters to those who choose to subscribe … and Google Analytics, to track usage of the site. No personally identifiable information is captured by Google Analytics.

#### Other important information

Except when required by law, 11points.com will not sell, distribute, or reveal your personal information without your consent. However, in rare circumstances, 11points.com may disclose some or all of your personally identifiable information to the government, law enforcement officials, or private parties if we, in our sole discretion, believe it necessary or appropriate to comply with the law; to respond to legal complaints; to comply with a legal process (including subpoenas); to protect the rights of 11points.com and/or its agents; to ensure the safety of the public or any person; and/or to prevent or stop any illegal, unethical, or legally questionable activity.

We may also disclose or transfer personal information collected through the website to third parties who acquire all or a portion of our business, which may be the result of a merger, consolidation, or purchase of all or a portion of our assets, or in connection with any bankruptcy or reorganization proceeding brought by or against us.

If 11points.com’s information practices change at some time in the future, policy changes will be posted to this page. Thanks for reading.

Updated: May 24, 2018
